《纸牌屋》前情提要...
Previously on House of Cards...
“我自愿承担此义务
"...that I take this obligation freely,
既无保留  也不逃避
"without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion."
我自愿承担此义务
"...that I take this obligation freely,
既无保留  也不逃避
"without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion."
我将尽职尽责”
"And that I Will Well..."
离总统只差一步
One heartbeat away from the presidency,
却不用一张选票
and not a single vote cast in my name.
民主也不过如此
Democracy is so overrated.
我更倾向于雷蒙德的想法
I lean more toward Raymond's thinking.
我们最不需要的就是自找麻烦
The last thing we want to do is rock the boat.
你答应过  会让这些都过去
You promised you'd make this all go away.
所以你得重新开始
And you starting over is the first step in that.
我已经重新开始了  不想再来一次了
I already started over. I don't want to start over again.
我也不想你这样
I wish you didn't have to.
华盛顿特区警察已经判定是一起意外
D.C. Police have ruled the death an accident.
你要放弃吗
Are you giving up on this?
这世上只有三个人...
There are only three people in the world...
知道他干了什么
...that know what he has done, and one of them is gone.
- 比如他们跟谁通过电话吗？ - 是的  跟谁通过电话  发过短信
- Like who they called? - Yeah, who they called, texted,
短信是什么内容
what they texted,
- 怎么进入深网 -  你想看的话我可以演示
- How do you access it? -I could show you if you want.
但我要提醒你  不要随便乱点
But I gotta warn you, be careful what you click.
这上面有些很疯狂的东西
Some crazy shit there, man.
提高退休年龄
Raising the age of retirement
是对美国梦不可容忍的侵蚀
is an unacceptable erosion of the American Dream.
如果共和党无法通过福利改革
If the Republicans fail to pass a reasonable Omnibus package
达成合理的综合解决方案
by demanding entitlement reform,
就会迫使联邦政府冻结开销
they will force the federal government into a spending freeze.
冻疮会长在他们手上  不是我们手上
The frostbite will be on their hands. Not ours.
这句是不是有点过了  冻疮那句
Do you think that's a bit much? The frostbite bit?
这是国情咨文  先生
Well, it's the State of the Union, sir.
我们想争取中部各州的赞同
We want to appeal to the flyover states.
他们会喜欢那句话的
They'll like that line.
我想要点更有力的句子
I want something more forceful.
他们手上沾满血
Blood on their hands?
不行
No.
把我们丢回冰河纪
Throw us back into the ice age.
我喜欢那句  克里斯蒂娜  我们试试
I like that, Christina. Let's try that.
琳达  克里斯蒂娜  你也过来
Linda. Christina, you come up here, too.
世上有两种副总统
There are two types of vice presidents.
受气包和斗牛士
Doormats and matadors.
你觉得我想做那种呢
Which do you think I intend to be?
雷蒙德
Raymond.
他在为内政操心
He's hung up on the domestic agenda.
一句关于中国的话也没说
Not a single word about China.
他的直觉是对的
His instincts are right.
如果政府在演讲后第二天关门
If the government shuts down one day after the speech,
他讲了什么就完全不重要了
not a single word in the speech matters.
我们得马上解决冻结开销的问题
We have to address the freeze now.
中国的事得靠后
China comes later.
两党为了改革的事吵了几个月了
Both parties have been wrangling over entitlements for months.
未来三天里
What makes you think a miracle
怎么可能出现奇迹
is gonna happen in the next three days?
我们给共和党他们想要的
We give the Republicans exactly what they want.
退休年龄
Retirement age?
对
Yes.
那是不可跨越的界限
That's a line in the sand we cannot cross.
我们最终还是得跨  所以何必争下去呢
We will cross it eventually, so why keep fighting it?
我可以推动参议院通过法案
I can push this through the Senate.
一旦我做到  总统就能在国情咨文中
And once I do, the president will announce
宣布两党达成了一项重要协议
a major bipartisan agreement in the State of the Union.
我们避免了政府关门
We avoid a government shutdown,
而功劳归白宫
and the White House gets credit.
太冒险了
It's a huge risk.
一旦失败  会颜面扫地
And if it fails, a huge embarrassment.
那也是丢我的脸
The embarrassment will be entirely my own.
这事我来担
This is on my shoulders.
即使如此  也不好说服总统
Even so, the president is gonna require some serious persuasion.
我去跟他谈
I'm happy to talk to him.
别  我来吧
No. No. I'll do it.
朋友去说  他更容易接受
He'll be more amenable if it comes from a friend.
没错  可信的密友
You're right. A trusted confidant.
我去试试水吧
Let me test the waters.
塔斯克党  成员  一人
The Cult of Tusk. Membership: one.
不过那个信徒恰好是
But that one disciple just so happens to be
自由世界最有权力的人
the most powerful man in the free world.
至少目前还是
For now.
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译 某羽   某豚   somehacker   章鱼X   葉某人
翻译 艾瑞卡   肉松   卢克·天意   小饭
蓝光版调整  timhal@HDWinG字幕组   后期 饿得慌
顾问 老杜   校对 草草   总监 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻译 HDWinG字幕组修正 请勿去掉制作者信息
《纸牌屋》
第二季  第三集
福利改革  把退休年龄提到67岁
The entitlements. Raising the age of eligibility to 67.
你们那边不会同意的
Your people will never go for it.
领导层同意  他们就会点头
They will if the leadership does.
而领导层会同意的
And the leadership will.
我还没断奶时这事就是两党的争议焦点
They fought us on this since I was in diapers.
假如我能说服我党同意提高退休年龄
Assuming that I can get this past my people and convince them,
你能说服你那边吗
can you convince yours?
这很困难
It's a tough sell.
你是参议院多数党领袖  赫克特
You're the Senate majority leader, Hector.
你不需要游说  可以直接命令
You don't have to sell. You can dictate.
你想要什么回报
What do you want in return?
一个正常运转的政府  避免开销冻结
A working government. We stave off the freeze.
你在《教育法案》上赢了
You won on education.
我们让你当上了副总统
We confirmed you as vice president.
共和党需要赢一次  弗兰克
The Republicans need a win, Frank.
我就是在提供赢的机会
And that's what I'm offering.
你们在福利改革上赢了
You get a win on entitlements.
我们避免了关门
We avoid a shutdown.
两党合作  双方都得分
Everyone gets points for bipartisanship.
你知道我担心谁
You know who I'm worried about.
柯蒂斯·哈斯
Curtis Haas.
他是个麻烦  弗兰克
He's a troublemaker, Frank.
还控制了你三分之一的党内成员
Who controls a third of your caucus.
他绝不会同意的
And he'll never go for this.
他就想看民主党不好过
He wants to see the Democrats suffer.
让他考虑一下
Just bring him to the table.
我只求这个
That's all I'm asking.
盖拉格小姐  我叫卢卡斯·古德温
Miss Gallagher? My name is Lucas Goodwin.
我是《华盛顿先驱报》的副主编
I'm a deputy editor at the Washington Herald.
古德温先生  拜托了
Mr. Goodwin, please.
只需要几分钟  我不求别的
Just a few moments. That's all I'm asking.
如果我想跟你说话  就会回你的电话
If I wanted to talk to you, I would have returned your calls.
你读过我的邮件吗
Did you read my emails?
读了  所以我没联系你
Yes. Which is why I didn't call.
请给我个机会解释
Give me a chance to walk you through it.
我得赶回白宫
I have to get back to the White House.
-抱歉  -彼得·罗素是被杀害的
- I'm sorry. - Peter Russo was killed.
放手
Let go.
佐伊·巴恩斯也是  我跟她是同事
So was Zoe Barnes. I was working with her.
住口  听我说...
Stop and listen --
弗兰克·安德伍德是幕后黑手
Frank Underwood is the one who did this.
听着  这是一派胡言
Listen! This is nuts.
酒驾记录  听证会  所有都是...
The DUI. The brack hearing. All of it was part of --
你不能再这样了  好吗
This has to stop. Okay?
安德伍德找过你了吗
Did Underwood talk to you?
-让你不要和别人说这些事吗  -没有
- Tell you not to speak with anybody? - No.
道格·斯坦普吗
Doug Stamper?
无论你以为发生了什么
Whatever you think happened,
无论是什么让你这样跟踪我...
whatever compelled you to stalk me like this --
你是唯一可能知道点什么的人
You're the only person who might know something,
能理解得了的人
who could understand.
我没有别人可以说这事了
I've got -- I've got no one else I can talk --
我不理解  也不想理解
I don't understand. And I don't want to.
行吗  这里面没什么内情
Okay? There's no story here.
拜托了  只要五分钟
Please, just five minutes.
想想你自己的行为
Just think about what you're doing.
守在楼外
Waiting outside of a building --
如果不是弗兰克·安德伍德  彼得可能还活着
Peter would still be alive if it wasn't for Frank Underwood.
我花了很大力气忘记彼得的事
I've worked really hard to put Peter behind me.
如果我再看到你  你再来找我
So if I see you again, if I hear from you again,
我不仅会报警
I'll not only contact the police,
还会让副总统知道你在对他说三道四
I'll let the vice president know what you're saying about him,
到时候你就等着特勤局来找上门吧
and then you can deal with the Secret Service, too.
都是正常的海外声音  中国那边有些杂音
It's the usual overseas chatter. Bit of a bum in China,
但我们觉得原因在贸易紧张
but we chalk that up to the trade tensions.
特勤局
Secret Service.
总统和副总统收到的死亡威胁数正常
Average number of death threats to both POTUS and the VP.
我们都交给了联调局的好伙伴们
We passed them along to our dear friends at the FBI.
联调局呢
FBI?
联调局向我们特勤局的
The FBI confirms the level of activity
好伙伴们确认了活动程度
of our dear friends at the Secret Service.
我们全部进行了追踪调查  没有高级别的威胁
We followed up on everything. No high-level threats.
我们没有需要直接
So nothing we need to report directly
向总统和副总统汇报的内容吗
to the president or vice president?
-没有  -谢谢  先生们
- No. - Thank you, gentlemen.
你发的邮件还有别人看过吗
The email you sent. Has anyone else seen it?
除了告知我的特工外  没有了
Except for the agent that alerted me, no.
其他机构可能会偶然看到
Other agencies might have stumbled upon this.
即使如此  他们大概也不会在意
Even so, they probably ignored it.
知道是谁发的帖子吗
Any idea who's making the posts?
深网论坛
Deep Web forums.
几乎无法追踪  很可能就是一个人
Almost impossible to trace. Lone wolf most likely.
我要你找到这个人
I want you to find him.
得有对生命构成直接威胁的证据
We need a direct threat to life.
副总统刚刚上任
The vice president just assumed office.
这类阴谋论绝不能甚嚣尘上
I can't have this conspiracy stuff going mainstream.
-这类传言一般会渐渐平息  -我不能冒这个险
- This sort of thing usually fizzles out -- - I can't take the chance.
你去找到这个人  把他关起来
I want you to find him and put him away.
-他并没犯罪  -但他有这个倾向
- He hasn't committed a crime. - But he wants to.
那就来个推波助澜
So help him.
那要耗费人力
That requires manpower.
你手里有人
You've got men.
会暴露我的  道格
It exposes me, Doug.
我一直给你透露消息  因为你是老朋友了
I've always kept you informed because you're an old pal
我信任你  但...
and I trust you. But...
你这是要我展开正式行动
We're talking about an operation.
我是你在白宫工作的老朋友
I'm an old pal who now works at the White House.
老朋友之间说说
Between old pals,
我这个行政部门联络官已经当得太久了
I've been stuck as the executive liaison for way too long.
您是否担心
How worried are you
您所在社区的学校内会发生大规模枪击事件
that a mass shooting could happen in a school in your community?
非常担心  比较担心  不怎么担心
Great deal, somewhat, not so much,
完全不担心  还是不确定
not at all, unsure?
你的声音很性感嘛  人怎么样
You sound hot. Are you hot?
先生
Sir...
比较性感  非常性感
Somewhat hot? A great deal hot?
挂断
林奇堡儿童医院  电话  传真
这里是林奇堡儿童医院小儿科
Lynchburg Children's, Pediatric Division.
我找谢莉尔·波斯纳
Can I talk to Cheryl Posner?
抱歉  她正在值班
Sorry. She's on duty right now.
我是她女儿
It's her daughter.
请稍候
Hold on one moment.
瑞秋  瑞秋吗
Rachel? Rachel?
甜心  你在听吗  请别...
Sweetheart, are you there? Please, do--
挂断
您好
Hello?
您好  杰伊先生
Hello, Mr. Jay.
我叫瑞秋
My name is Rachel
代表全国枪支教育中心向您致电
and I'm calling on behalf of the National Firearm Education Center.
您能和我简单聊聊
Would you be able to speak with me briefly
您对枪支立法和第二修正案的看法吗
regarding firearm legislation and Second Amendment legislation?
你就是薇拉力荐的人
So, you're Willa's top choice.
那我丈夫和我为什么要选择你呢
Why should you be my husband's and my top choice?
在过去十年中
Over the past 10 years
关于你们夫妇的报道加起来还不到
the two of you combined have gotten less coverage
内布拉斯加州资浅众议员的平均水平
than the average junior congressman from Nebraska.
我们不想太受瞩目
Well, we don't seek the spotlight.
我不是说你们非要如此
I'm not suggesting you should.
但如果我没猜错
But am I correct in assuming
你丈夫会是一位行事积极的副总统
that your husband will be an active vice president?
想让媒体不去关注积极的副总统是比较难的
It's harder to keep an active VP out of the press than in it,
但我们可以让媒体刚好有些料可追
but it's possible if we give the media just enough
不至于什么都拿不到
to keep them from starving.
你在哪长大的  康纳
Where'd you grow up, Connor?
德州  和你一样
Texas. Just like you.
达拉斯吗
Dallas?
拉布克
Lubbock.
我想改口音可比你们难多了
I had a much thicker accent to get rid of you than y'all.
你怎么知道我有口音
How do you know I had one?
你俩第一次共同接受采访
Your first joint interview,
86年你丈夫竞选州议员时
when your husband was running for state assembly in '86.
网上有吗
That's on the internet?
没有  我联系了格林维尔当地的电视台
No. No. I contacted the local affiliate in Greenville.
他们不愿邮寄录像带
They wouldn't send me the tapes via mail,
我就亲自去资料库看了
so I went down there and watched in their vault.
跑到南卡罗莱纳吗
To South Carolina?
应聘就得做好准备工作
When I want a job, I do my homework.
很期待你的表现
I look forward to seeing what you come up with.
谢谢  安德伍德太太
Thank you, Mrs. Underwood.
周四见
Thursday.
这怎么能算胜利
I don't see how this is a victory for us.
我们要么面临开销冻结
Our choices are the freeze,
民主党会为这个饱受责难
which the Democrats get blamed for, or --
不一定  共和...
Not necessarily. The Republi--
我们也一样会受责难
No, which we definitely get blamed for.
-要么给他们  -福利改革吗  弗兰克
- Or we offer them -- - Entitlements, Frank?
我们已经表了态  不能回头了
We took a stand. We can't turn back now.
我宁可让政府停转
I'd rather see the government grind to a halt.
如果头条是
Think of the headline:
《民主党高层通过法案  避免开销冻结》
"Democrat Leadership Enacts Entitlement Reform, Staves Off Freeze."
这是团结和进步的表现
We show unity. We offer progress.
我们说服几个中坚保守派吧
Let's convert some lifelong conservatives.
门多萨答应合作了吗
You have Mendoza's assurance he'll work with us?
是的
I do.
我可不想把头伸出去
I don't want to put our necks out there
等人家落刀
just to have the guillotine fall.
不会的  我们也会一起伸出去
You won't. My neck will be right out there with you.
弗兰西斯晕血
Francis faints at the sight of blood.
不会允许他们割伤他的皮肤的
He'd never let them break the skin.
敬团结
To unity.
不不不  别这样
No, no, no, no, no. Come on.
拉瑞  能来一趟吗
Larry, can you come by?
我电脑不知道怎么了
Something weird's going on with my computer.
谢谢
Thanks.
别这样
Come on!
怎么回事
Hey, what's the problem?
没事  我修好了
Nothing. It's fine. Uh, I fixed it.
好吧
Okay. Cool.
放松
深呼吸
投降吧
你要的我能给你  亲爱的
还不够革新
It's not as progressive as I'd like.
不够极端吧
You mean radical.
退休年龄升到67岁  2055年前政府都能负担福利
Raising retirement age to 67 makes entitlements solvent until 2055.
还能省一万亿
And it saves us over a trillion dollars
不花纳税人的钱
without a single penny of taxpayer income.
改到68岁能再省三千亿
68 would give us another 300 billion.
我还想禁止提前退休
And I'd like to eliminate early retirement.
完全禁止吗
Entirely?
不可能
Forget it.
68岁退  64岁早退呢
What about 68 and 64?
我要对选民负责
I have a responsibility to my constituents.
我承诺过某些问题绝不妥协
I promised I wouldn't waver when it comes to things --
民共两党票数僵持时  茶党的倾向能决定局势
难道要让茶党决定财政立法吗
Are we really going to allow the Tea Party to determine fiscal legislation?
我从没指望他们帮忙
I've never been beholden to the Tea Party.
得了吧  柯蒂斯
Come on, Curtis.
没有茶党政治行动委员会
You wouldn't have won reelection
给你的一千万  你也赢不了重选
if their PACs hadn't dumped 10 million into your campaign.
如果他们对缩减开支的看法
If their definition of budgetary conservatism
与我不谋而合  那就正好...
happens to overlap with mine, that's a function--
柯蒂斯  柯蒂斯  友善一点
Curtis. Curtis. Let's show some goodwill.
68岁和64岁可以接受吗
Can you stomach 68 and 64?
马上生效吗
Effective immediately?
五年以后
Five years from now.
没兴趣
Not interested.
我们不能突然抛出这个提议
Well, you know we can't throw this on people without any warning.
得给他们时间消化
They need some time to digest.
对不起  就是不行
I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
好吧  回去跟你们的幕僚和同事商量一下
Okay. Meet with your staff. Consult with your colleagues.
我也回去商量  明天再谈
I'll consult with mine. And let's talk tomorrow.
好吧  没问题
All right. I can agree to that.
这第一步很不错
But this is a good first step.
修正案通过后  法案进行表决时
How do we make sure Curtis can't filibuster
柯蒂斯阻挠议事怎么办
when we get the amendment passed?
如果能走到那步
Assuming we do.
只跟你说  我觉得我们可以改变他的想法
Between you and me, I'm sure we can turn him around.
我只是不想冒险
I just want to be on the safe side.
我们让修正案的表决
We make sure the passage of the amendment
成为法案表决的一部分
constitutes the passage of the bill.
事先约定
By previous agreement.
没错  修正案一通过
Yeah, that's right. We pass the amendment,
就完事了
and then we're done. Wham, bam.
能落到纸上吗
Can we put that in writing?
让艾瑞克森找我吧
Have Erikson reach out to me.
非常感谢
Muchos gracias.
慢用
There you go.
卢卡斯·古德温
Lucas Goodwin?
打开我  亲爱的
晚上好  卢卡斯
Good evening, Lucas.
对着麦克风说话
Speak into the microphone.
你是谁
Who are you?
返回主屏  打开另一个应用
Go to the home screen. Open the other app.
先告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
你调查过我  想必已经知道我是谁了
You've done your research. You know who I am.
我怎么知道那是不是你的真实身份
I -- I know who you claim to be.
你要是现在还不相信我  那就不必谈了
And if you're not convinced by now, goodbye.
别别
Wait.
听你的  我返回主屏了
All right, I'm on the home screen.
打开验证程序
Open the notary app.
这是什么
What is this?
确保你不为执法部门工作
To ensure you aren't law enforcement.
我不是
I'm -- I'm not.
那就签了它
Then sign.
怎么签
How?
把你的拇指按在摄像头上  然后点"扫描"
Hold your thumb to the camera and press "Capture."
身份验证  指纹扫描
万一你是给执法部门的呢
How do I know you're not law enforcement?
要么签了这文件  要么走人
Sign the document or walk away.
身份验证  指纹扫描
好了  我签好了
All right. I did it.
点"发送"
Press "Send."
发送到哪
Where is this going?
我用了伊朗和其他12个国家的代理
I'm VPNing through Iran and 12 other countries.
你不用担心  链接很安全
Don't worry. It's secure.
最后一件事
Now, one last thing.
我要《华盛顿先驱报》
I need the two-step verification code
内部服务器的两步验证码
for the Herald's internal servers.
我根本不知道该怎么做
I -- I don't -- I don't even know how to do that.
你当然知道  看你的邮箱
Yes, you do. Check your email.
把这平板毁了  尤其要把产品序列号抹干净
Destroy the iPad, especially the serial number
邮件记牢之后就删掉
and delete the email after you've memorized it.
祝你好运
Good luck.
还在吗
Hello?
雷蒙德  还在听吗
Raymond, are you there?
在
Yeah.
抱歉  弗兰克  我还以为看到了一只印加地鸠
Sorry, Frank. I -- I thought I saw an Inca dove.
肯定是冬迁飞错方向了
Must have flown the wrong direction for winter.
你那边好像风挺大  你在哪呢
It sounds windy. Where are you?
在我家楼顶  装了个野鸟喂食器
Top of my building. Got a bird feeder up here.
总统的工作做得不错  听说他同意了
Nice work with the President. I hear we have a green light.
他一开始也不愿意  但还是让步了
He pushed back in the beginning, but yeah.
他的写手正在改讲稿
His writers are reworking the speech now.
我这边也快成了  五年后  68退休  64早退
I'm very close to a deal.  68/64 in five years.
按说好的削减开支
Spending cuts as discussed.
说定了吗
Is that rock solid?
就差握手签字了
Soon as we shake hands.
那是谁在作梗
What's the hold-up?
柯蒂斯·哈斯  不过也在意料之中
Curtis Haas, which isn't a surprise.
我过会儿就和他见面  他是最后的障碍了
I'm meeting with him soon. He's the final hurdle.
时间掐得太正好了  弗兰克
Cutting it pretty close, Frank.
这可是历史性的时刻
Well, this is -- this is historic.
约翰逊当总统时共和党人就想推动福利改革了
The Republicans have wanted entitlement reform since Johnson.
柯蒂斯会同意的
Curtis will come around.
另外我们得在讲稿里提到延迟退休的事
In the meantime we should get the new retirement age into the speech.
我看还是别说得太详细  弗兰克
I would stay away from the specifics, Frank.
就算参议院通过了  众议院没准也...
I mean, I-- even if it passes, the House might--
我对众议院的了解
I know the House better
比你对鸟深入得多  雷蒙德
than you know birds, Raymond.
相信我  他们肯定会通过参议院的版本
Believe me when I say they'll pass the Senate version.
那我去跟总统说说
I'll talk to the President.
但这事绝不能有差错
Just make sure this is airtight.
多谢你  什么事
Thank you. What is it?
卢卡斯·古德温
Lucas Goodwin.
先驱报的那个
From the Herald.
他肯定在和佐伊一起调查
He must have been working with Zoe.
他知道多少
How much does he know?
不会比她多
No more than she did.
她知道的可不少
She knew enough.
我在办  先生
I'm on it, sir.
有证据吗
Proof?
还没有
Not yet.
怎么搞的  道格
Jesus, Doug.
局面在控制中  我只是想告诉你一声
It's under control. I just thought you should be aware.
我在跟总统  共和党和塔斯克周旋
I'm juggling the President, the Republicans, Tusk.
-我不能...  -你就继续忙你的
- I can't -- - And you should stay focused on that.
古德温交给我处理  你无须担心
Goodwin's on my plate. Not yours.
一直到20世纪
It wasn't until the 20th century
客观主义理念才成为主流观念
that the notion of noble objectivism came into the forefront.
但事实就是事实
But facts are facts.
1992年  事实  有人拿出一张
1992. Fact: George Bush, Sr.
老布什询问售货扫描机是如何工作的照片
is shown asking how a grocery scanner works,
进而攻击他无知
and he gets nailed for it.
真相是  他们向他展示的是一个新模型机
Fact? They were showing him a new model.
他只是在问新机器与旧机器的差别
He was asking how the new one was different than the old one.
好奇而已  并非无知
Curiosity, not ignorance.
但语境的缺失却传达了一个更有冲击力的观点
But the lack of context told a more powerful narrative.
在对事实的诸多整理中
There is no arrangement of acts
没有哪个是...完全客观的
that is, uh, purely objective.
我们总算可以做点什么了  终于有手段了
We can finally do something. We have the means to act.
哪个毛都没长全的少年黑客...
Some teenage pimple-faced hacker --
这是很高端的入侵
This was a sophisticated infiltration.
不是小孩子做得出来的
It's not the work of a child.
你看  邮件在这里
Look. Here's the email.
机器人希洛尼摩斯
Hieronymus Bot.
希洛尼摩斯  古希腊史学家  以公正著名
联邦调查局已经追捕他很多年了
The FBI's been hunting him for years.
卢卡斯  听我说
Lucas, listen to me --
如果我们拿到了这些记录
If we get these records,
我需要你帮忙理顺时间先后
I'll need your help tracking timelines,
拼凑整件事的发展...
piecing together the chronology of the --
不  你只想找个人安慰你
No. You want somebody to hold your hand
告诉你  做这些无用功没什么不对
and say it's okay to go on this fucking goose chase.
你不该在伊萨卡教书  你的能力不止如此
You shouldn't be teaching in Ithaca. You're better than that.
-你该回华盛顿  -我就该待在这里
- You should be back home -- - I belong here.
对一群宿醉未消的英语专业大学生唠叨吗
Droning on to a bunch of hungover English majors?
没错
Exactly.
你对真相的看法是错的  客观事实是存在的
You're wrong about the truth. There is objective truth.
他杀了她
He killed her.
你知道这是事实
You know it's a fact.
事实就是
Here's a fact.
我妈最多只剩10到15年了
My mom has 10, 15 years left at best.
我毕业后加起来也没有上个月跟她相处时间久
I've seen her more in the past month than since I left for school.
这里更简单  也很安静
It's simpler here. It's quiet.
我需要这样的环境  她需要我
I need that. She needs me.
很抱歉  卢卡斯
I'm sorry, Lucas.
抱歉我那晚做出了那样的反应
I'm sorry that night how I reacted.
很遗憾你失去了你的女友
I'm sorry you lost your girlfriend.
很遗憾世界就是这么操蛋
I'm sorry the world is this fucked up.
我是真心的
I really am.
但我帮不了你
But I can't help you.
其他人在哪里
Where's everyone else?
我昨天给你帮了个倒忙
I did you a disservice yesterday.
不该在整个领导层面前让你为难
We shouldn't have put you on the spot in front of all the leadership.
请坐  柯蒂斯
Have a seat, Curtis.
我们知道你必须坚守立场
We know that you have an obligation to take a firm stance,
但承诺福利改革是你竞选的核心
but entitlement reform is something you ran on,
现在唾手可得了
and now it's within your grasp.
说说你的顾虑吧
So tell us your fears.
顾虑就是共和党又会赢一把
That the Democrats get another win.
我们在中期选举中失利
We suffer in the midterms,
下一届国会就会废除协议
and the next Congress dismantles the agreement.
你觉得我们在玩花招
You think we're being disingenuous.
我的选民不信任政府
My constituents don't trust the administration.
我不能让他们觉得我们受到了蒙骗
I can't have them thinking the wool's been pulled over our eyes.
如我所料  赫克特
As I suspected. Hector?
弗兰克和我建议
Frank and I propose this:
我们加入一项简单多数条款
We include a super majority point of order
十年内不再就这个问题进行新的立法讨论
against revisiting the issue for 10 years.
白纸黑字写下来
You have it in black and white.
达成一项长期的严肃承诺  不会被撤销
A serious, long-term commitment with no opportunity to dismantle.
这是加在其他要求之上
And that's on top of everything else we asked for.
退伍军人事务管理局和联邦救灾署的经费维持不变
VA services and FEMA stay at current levels.
其他机构的经费削减为你提议的80%到100%
Everything else at 80 to 100 percent of the cuts you propose.
你赢了  柯蒂斯
You get your win, Curtis.
我们只想避免灾难
We just avoid disaster.
也许国家应该见识一下灾难
Maybe the country needs to see what disaster looks like.
茶党的影响力很大  而你又为他们宣传
The Tea Party has a strong voice, and you're its bullhorn.
让你的人民看到  这份影响力能决定法律
Show your people that voice can translate into law
而不仅仅是激昂的口号
and not just add to the noise.
15年内不得重谈  10年不够
15 years before revisitation. Not 10.
可以
Okay.
如果我们通过法案后  众议院没有通过
And if the House fails to pass the bill after we do,
你得公开谴责你们党派造了这种僵局
you go on record blaming your own party for the gridlock.
我们这就算达成协议了
I believe we have a deal.
你在听什么
What are you listening to?
抱歉  我关...
I'm sorry. I'll turn...
别  很好听  我能听吗
No, it's nice. Can I listen?
我的耳朵很干净  我保证
My ears are clean. I promise.
谢谢
Thanks.
-真美  -是啊
- It's beautiful. - Yeah.
好哀伤
It's so sad.
能让我放松
It helps me relax.
今天很辛苦吗
Long day?
我在客服中心上班
I work at a call center.
一小时打电话给200个陌生人  是挺辛苦
So, yeah. 200 strangers an hour.
我就不打扰你了
I'll leave you alone.
你大概也不想再和陌生人聊天了
You probably don't want to talk to another one.
没关系  你不挂我电话就行
It -- it's all right. As long as you don't hang up on me.
你会和他们聊天吗  那些陌生人
Do you ever just talk to them? The strangers?
我们不允许
We're not allowed to.
换了我  肯定想问问他们是什么样
All I would want to do is ask them about who they are.
你呢  你做什么工作
What about you? What do you do?
我...在书店和托儿所上班
I, um, I work at the bookstore and the daycare center.
冬离友谊会  通往平静之路
别人第一次给我宣传册时
I had that same look on my face
我也是这个表情
the first time somebody handed me one of those.
我只是...不信教
Yeah, I'm -- I'm just -- I'm not religious.
留着吧  看不看都无所谓
Just keep it. Check it out, or don't.
我们那儿有非常棒的音乐
We've got really good music there.
谢谢你
I'm -- thank you.
众议院向参议院提交了一份法案
The House sent a bill to the Senate.
和弗兰克期待的反馈完全不同
What Frank wants to send back bears zero resemblance.
因为那是两党联合的  不像我们的这份
Because it's bipartisan. Unlike ours.
听着像弗兰克的话
That sounds like something Frank would say.
我不是弗兰克
I'm not Frank.
他是你办公室的常客
He has a desk in your office.
如果法案在参议院通过
If this bill passes in the Senate --
不可能
It won't.
我们得有所准备  鲍勃
We should be prepared, Bob.
那我就拭目以待了
Well, I'm prepared to wait and see.
下午愉快  女士们
Have a good afternoon, ladies.
女士们
"Ladies"?
他受到了威胁
He's threatened.
蠢猪一个
He's a pig.
给他点时间
Give him time.
以前他身边有两个中年白人男子
He used to have two white middle-aged guys at his side.
现在他只能依靠一个黑人和一个小他20岁的女人
Now he's got a black guy and a woman 20 years his junior.
可这女人会开枪
Who knows how to shoot a rifle.
我们得继续劝他
We just need to keep at him.
什么事
Yes?
凯特琳娜·罗德里格斯在四号线
Catalina Rodriguez is on line four.
你先下去
Give me a moment.
凯特琳娜
Catalina.
泰德告诉我是你干的
Ted told me it was you.
你在听吗
You there?
是的  我在听
Yes, I'm here.
媒体对我们穷追不舍
The press won't leave us alone.
他们连续几周跑过来
For weeks they're showing up,
想拍到我和艾米莉的照片
trying to get pictures of me and Emily.
不是我泄的密
It wasn't me.
只有你知情
You're the only one who knew.
我不知道事情怎么会泄露
I do-- I don't know how the story got out.
泰德何必对我撒谎呢
Why would Ted lie abut that?
我不知道  也许他感到羞愧
I don't know. Maybe -- maybe he's ashamed.
那我该怎么办  他们什么时候才会放过我们
So what do I do? When will they leave us alone?
我也不知道  凯特琳娜
I -- I don't know, Catalina.
我受不了这样的生活
I can't live like this.
我很抱歉  我不知该说什么
I'm s-- I'm sorry. I don't know what to say.
艾米莉还好吗
How -- how is Emily doing?
凯特琳娜
Catalina?
他自信满满
He's very confident.
没错  但他有那个本事吗
Yeah, but does he have what it takes?
等他拿出媒体方案就知道了
We'll see when I get his media plan.
他个性如何
What about his personality?
迷人  直接  思维缜密
Charming. Direct. Very thorough.
他找到了86年我们第一次一起接受采访的录像
He found our first interview together, in '86.
我很想重温一下  他有副本吗
I would love to see that. Does he have a copy?
我想没有  电视台只允许他在台里看
I don't think so. The TV station made him watch it there.
我们该录下来给总统和第一夫人看的
We should screen that for the president and the first lady.
让他们学学怎么接受采访
Show 'em how it's done.
克里斯蒂娜
Christina...
她怎么了
What about her?
你有没有注意到她和总统有什么不正常
Have you noticed anything strange between her and the president?
什么意思
How do you mean?
昨天我在走道里碰见他们
I passed them in the hall yesterday.
他们看上去  我说不好  很亲密
And they seem -- I don't know -- very intimate.
预备会议上他们是挺热络的
They did seem cozy at the prep session.
你觉得...
Do you think...?
不  不一定
No. Not necessarily.
不过这想法挺有意思
An interesting thought, though.
抱歉打扰  先生
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
我们在吃午饭
We're having lunch.
共和党人变卦了
The Republicans are backing out.
门多萨的幕僚长给我提了醒
Mendoza's chief of staff just gave me the heads-up.
马上帮我接门多萨
Get Mendoza on the phone.
是柯蒂斯·哈斯  他临阵退缩了
It's Curtis Haas. He got cold feet.
笼子  差不多像那样  不过
Cages. It's really kinda like but,
但大家会看  挺逗的
you know, people look at 'em. It's kind of fun.
我收到你邮件了
I got your email.
你现在有空吗
Now good for you?
当然  我过会儿打给你
Yeah, sure. Can I call you right back?
你究竟想问什么
What exactly did you need to know?
我们在做网络战的后续报道
We're doing some follow-up pieces on the cyber warfare thing.
我就想问问内行人知不知道
I just wanted to get a layman's understanding
中国人会如何越过防火墙
of how the Chinese might get through a firewall.
挺复杂的  不过我可以演示下基本原理
It's a bit complicated, but I could show you the basics.
那足够了
That's all I need.
输入响应码
我们使用的是标准多层体系结构
We use a standard N-tier architecture.
就像多层面包做成的大三明治
Think of it like a big sandwich with layers of bread.
每层之间夹着生菜  番茄  烤牛肉之类的
Between each is the lettuce, the tomato, the roast beef, whatever.
我现在输入的是组织代码
What I'm pulling up here is the org code,
隔离了数据库
which, uh, separates the database --
该死  我忘了马上要和销售部门开会
Shit. I forgot there's a meeting with sales in a couple minutes.
你想晚点继续吗
You want to do this later?
不用  我现在跑过去
No. I'll just run over
跟他们说我要晚几分钟到  马上回来
and let them know I'll be a few minutes late. Be right back.
好  我就在这儿
Cool. I'll be here.
我拿到手机了
很好  发送请求密码
好的
Okay.
快点快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
来了
There.
快回复啊
Come on.
我进去了  干得好
晚上9点  西北区  哥伦比亚街  6697号见
好
Okay.
切记
删除短信
好嘞
Go.
出什么事了
Something wrong?
我找不着手机了  真奇怪
Can't find my phone. It -- it's weird.
刚刚还在的
I had it just a minute ago.
找到了  不好意思
Here it is. Sorry about that.
没事
No problem.
那个多层体系结构
So the, uh, N-tier architecture.
我刚说的那个高科技三明治
The high-tech sandwich I was talking about.
我以为门多萨愿意合作
I thought Mendoza was willing to work with us.
他是愿意  问题在柯蒂斯·哈斯
He is. The problem is Curtis Haas.
你跟他谈过了吗
And have you spoken with him?
他办公室不回我们电话
His office isn't returning our calls.
门多萨也是
Neither is Mendoza's --
我不该让步的
I should've stuck to my guns.
明天下午才开始投票
The vote isn't until tomorrow afternoon.
我一早就会联系门多萨
I'll reach out to Mendoza first thing in the --
这可是国情咨文  弗兰克
This is the State of the Union, Frank.
我不能陷入尴尬境地
I won't be left in limbo.
如果我们得重写演讲
If we need to start rewriting that speech now,
我一分钟也不想耽误
I don't want to waste a minute.
我能扭转局面  先生
I can turn this around, sir.
雷蒙德告诉我这是你的点子
You know, Raymond told me this was your idea.
做出妥协
To pursue this compromise.
只是提出建议
I suggested it as an option.
他说是你逼他蹚这浑水的
He said you bullied him into it,
他认为这是个错误的决定
that he thought it was a -- a mistake.
如果他这么反对  他就应该劝阻你
If he felt so strongly, he should have advised you otherwise.
雷蒙德不是政客
Raymond is not a politician.
他依赖于我们的政治意见
He relies on our political expertise
正如我们依靠他的商业头脑
as much as we rely on his business acumen.
或许我们应该到真出现问题再相互指责
Maybe we shouldn't point fingers until there's a problem.
你管这不叫问题
Oh, you wouldn't call this a problem.
在成为问题之前解决掉就不是问题
Not if it's solved before it becomes one.
我要的是个能管理好国会的副总统
You see, I wanted a Vice President who can manage Congress.
而不是个不自量力的人
Not one who bites off more than he can chew.
那就相信你做出了正确的决定  先生
Then have faith you made the right choice, sir.
我的信念正在迅速地消失殆尽了
Whatever faith I have is quickly evaporating.
别给政府丢脸  弗兰克
Don't humiliate the administration, Frank.
你也是其中一员了
You're part of it now.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我们谈完了
We're done.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
帮我接内线
Give me the private line, please.
塔斯克挡我道  古德温对我穷追不舍
Tusk is blocking my way. Goodwin at my heels.
现在一步也不能错
There can be no false steps now.
越往上爬  尔虞我诈越多
The higher up the mountain, the more treacherous the path.
卢卡斯·古德温去找她了
Lucas Goodwin went up to visit her.
他们可能也会来找你
They may be looking for you.
没人找过我  应该没人知道我在这儿
Nobody's contacted me. I don't think anyone knows I'm here.
那我们要确保你不会被人发现
Then we need to make sure it stays that way.
避免不必要的交谈
Don't speak to anyone you don't have to.
不要去不必要的地方
Don't go anywhere you don't need to be.
告诉我你听到我说的了
Tell me you heard what I said.
听到了  我知道了
I heard you. I get it.
我没事
I'm fine.
-敷点冰  -我说了我没事
- Put some ice on it. - I said it's okay.
这是什么
What is this?
你现在还翻我的垃圾吗
What, are you going through my garbage now?
在公交上别人给我的
Someone gave it to me on the bus.
有人联系你  就来告诉我
You let me know if anyone contacts you.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
没事
No worries.
现在你要纹多少
How much more you want to do right now?
填满这一块吗
Fill in this area?
嗯  然后下面再多加一个罂粟
Yeah. And, uh, one more poppy down here.
一次做这么多啊
That's a lot for one sitting.
我知道
I know.
好吧
Okay.
弗兰西斯
Francis?
这就走吗
You're heading in?
门多萨起的早
Mendoza's an early riser.
你会解决好的
You'll figure this out.
我得证明副总统不吃素的
I need to prove what the Vice President is capable of.
别向他们证明  向我证明
Don't prove it to them. Prove it to me.
柯蒂斯抓着我的要害  弗兰克
Curtis has me by the tea bags, Frank.
没他我的党派就要乱套
I don't have a working majority without him.
可他不是多数党领袖
He wasn't elected leader.
是没错  但我也得选边站
True. But I have to pick my battles.
你要是在预算问题上无法控制他
If you can't control him on budgetary issues --
不光是他  还有听命于他的15个参议员
It's not just him. It's the 15 senators he has under his thumb.
没他们支持我就不能连任
I won't be the leader next year if they turn on me.
他想我们求他  把他找来
So he wants to be courted. Sit him down --
我试过和他谈了  但他不肯让步
I already tried talking to him. He wouldn't budge.
那我们一起去跟他谈
Then we'll both talk to him.
他已经表明立场了
He's made his position clear.
我们都在这张桌子旁握手了
We all shook hands at this table.
我最多只能保证限制替代修正案
The most I can do is put the substitute amendment
表决前的辩论
on the floor with limited debate.
你们那边公开怎么说随你们便
Now, your people can say whatever they want for the record.
但我们会投票否决修正案
But we're gonna vote the amendment down.
我对象征性姿态不敢兴趣
I am not interested in symbolic gestures.
我只能做到这样
That's all I can offer.
你的勇气哪去了
Where's your courage?
我权力有限  弗兰克
My power has limits, Frank.
再有五个共和党人  你那票就定胜负了
Five Republicans makes you the deciding vote.
现在很难说
Now, it's highly doubtful
我们能不能让他们违反党派意志投票
we can get them to vote against their own party.
但他们可以弃权
But they might abstain.
那需要10人弃权
You'd need 10.
福利问题是共和党人的长期追求
Entitlement is the Republicans' white whale.
我至少能说通两个人
I can get at least two of 'em to flip.
那就只需要六票弃权
And you'd only need six abstaining.
艾瑞克森已经在打电话了
Erikson's already making calls.
唐纳
Donner?
还有普拉斯科
And Pulaski.
给我一份名单  我找几个人一起上阵
All right. Get me a call list so I can tag-team with him.
在这儿
Got it right here.
我们得使狠招
We have to get medieval.
要说议会程序
When it comes to parliamentary procedure,
没有哪条规定我不知道  先生
there's not a rule I don't know, sir.
给我找到能钻空子的
Find me the ones we can bend.
马克  你是个明白人
Mark, you're a sensible man.
是  我知道  我懂
Yes, I -- I know -- I understand.
如果  跟你说
What if -- tell you what.
如果你选区内的两家退伍军人医院  对  两家
What if both VA hospitals in your district -- yes, both of them.
别挂  谁
Hold on. Who?
莫里亚蒂
Moriarty.
我答应给他的牲牛研究中心拨款
I promised him an amendment for his bovine research center.
这就有六票了
That makes six.
马克  如果我能给两家医院提供资金
Mark, if I can get you funding for both,
你愿跟我们合作吗
are you with us?
非常好
Excellent.
你这几天来白宫
You come by the White House
跟我共进午餐吧
and have lunch with me sometime soon.
再见  数目够了
Bye-bye. We have the numbers.
你打断点名之后
Once you break the quorum call
会有些麻烦
it's gonna be a little tricky.
我们路上说
Tell me on the way.
先生  先生
Sir. Sir.
-我们票数可能不占多数  -什么
- We might not have a majority. - What?
民主党在挖墙脚
The Dems are poaching people.
唐纳  普拉斯基  可能还有别人
Donner, Pulaski. Maybe more.
投票通过修正案吗
Voting for the amendment?
部分支持  其余弃权  我还在查是谁
Some. Others abstaining. I'm still trying to figure out who.
我们得推迟  弄清到底是怎么回事
We need to delay and figure out what the fuck's going on.
点名  离休会还有49小时
Quorum call. There's 49 hours until the recess.
一小时叫一个人来
We call a name an hour.
艾文戴尔先生
Mr. Avendale?
到
Here.
抱歉  你坐了我的位置
Excuse me. I do believe you're sitting in my chair.
德鲁里先生  现在进行到哪里了
Mr. Drewry, what is the order of business.
我们正在点名  先生
We are in a quorum call, sir.
那你怎么不点名呢
Then why aren't you calling the roll?
在点名  先生  不着急
We are, sir. In a deliberate manner.
速度快点吧
Let's speed it up.
布朗先生
Mr. Brown?
到
Here.
动作再快点
More expeditious than that.
-博尔先生  -到
- Mr. Burr? - Here.
-坎特维尔女士  -到
- Ms. Cantwell? - Here.
西里尼先生
Mr. Cerini?
到
Check.
康维尔
Cornwall?
到
Here.
科森先生
Mr. Colson?
道斯特女士
Ms. Douster
到
Here.
法定人数够了  我们票数不够
They have a quorum. We don't have the numbers.
出去  让我们的人都出去
Out. Let's get all our people out.
-达默尔先生  达令先生  -到
- Mr. Demerell. Mr. Darling. - Here.
-达斯瓦尼先生  -到
- Mr. Daswani. - Here.
-唐纳先生  -再快点
- Mr. Donner. - Faster.
道本先生  德怀尔先生
Mr. Dobben, Mr. Dwyer.
-埃伦伯格  安格  艾瑞克森  -到
- Erinburgh, Engel, Erikson. - Here.
菲尔德  法瑞森  詹特里
Feld, Ferrison, Gentry.
哈斯先生
Mr. Haas.
-怀特豪斯先生  -到
- Mr. Whitehouse. - Here.
维克先生  怀登先生
Mr. Wicker. Mr. Wyden.
副总统先生  没有达到法定人数
Mr. President, a quorum is not present.
主席允许少数党领袖  艾瑞克森先生发言
The chair recognizes the minority leader, Mr. Erikson.
主席先生
Mr. President,
我提议命令警卫官
I move to direct the sergeant at arms
强制缺席参议员到场
to compel the attendance of absent Senators;
对于无故缺席的所有参议员
that warrants for the arrests of all senators not sick nor excused
请会议主席签发逮捕令予以逮捕
be issued under the signature of the presiding officer.
对动议进行表决  同意者说"赞成"
The question is on the motion. All those in favor say "Aye"
赞成
Aye.
反对者说"反对"
All those opposed, "Nay."
反对
Nay.
同意者占多数  动议通过
The ayes have it, and the motion is agreed to.
我命令警卫官
The sergeant of arms is hereby instructed
强制缺席参议员到场
to compel the attendance of absent senators.
回国会的感觉真好
It feels good to be back in Congress.
现在民主党人已经授予国会警察
The Democrats have now empowered the Capitol Police
在必要时逮捕缺席参议员的权利
to arrest absent members if necessary.
共和党参议员柯蒂斯·哈斯
According to Republican Senator Curtis Haas,
福利改革修正案的坚决反对者之一
one of the staunchest opponents of the entitlement amendment,
这样说道  副总统正在
the vice president is, quote,
"用暴政取代民主
"Replacing democracy with tyranny.
他已经将参议院变成了国会里的极权国家"
He's transformed the Senate into a police state within the Capitol."
但是
But --
现在想躲避媒体更难了
It'll be even harder to stay out of the news now.
那为什么还要一起接受采访
Then why the joint interview?
我又看了一遍南卡罗来纳的采访
I watched the South Carolina one again.
说服他们给了我一份拷贝
Convinced them to make me a copy.
非常有感染力  给你
It's powerful. Here you go.
我猜你可能想留一份
I thought you might want it.
采访中有一个瞬间  你用手帮他捋头发
There's a moment where you ran your fingers through his hair.
非常亲密  非常有人情味
It's intimate and human.
单是那一个瞬间就足以让我为你丈夫投票
That moment alone would've made me want to vote for your husband.
像这样的小事  能给你几个月的清净
Something like that will buy you months of flying beneath the radar.
你想让谁来进行采访
And who do you have in mind to conduct the interview?
这代表我被录用了吗
Does this mean I have the job?
这代表你还没出局
It means you still haven't been ruled out.
我就当是有进步了
Well, I'll consider that progress.
这里是民主党议员的衣帽间  赫克特
This is the Democratic cloak room, Hector.
你们的在另一边
Yours is on the other side.
你的招数不会成功的
What you're doing won't work.
有可能会  所以你大老远的跑过来了
It might. Which is why you made the long walk over here.
冰水
Ice water?
我的人正坐着各种交通工具赶过来
I have my people in planes, trains, and automobiles.
我只需要六票达到法定人数
All I need is six to make my quorum.
想想我有26票能干什么
Think what I can do with 26 votes.
现在我都有45票了
And I've got 45.
你的人再怎么赶也没这么快吧
You won't be able to get your planes and trains back here fast enough.
我愿赌一把
I'll roll those dice.
会议警卫官的工作做得非常好
The sergeant at arms is very good at his job.
这样正可以让柯蒂斯明白  究竟谁是老大
And this is a perfect way to show Curtis who's in charge.
我这是在帮你  赫克特
I'm doing you a favor, Hector.
告诉我你想要什么
Tell me what you want.
我一直想要的东西  我们达成的协议
What I've always wanted. The package we shook hands on.
然后我就把参议院还给你
Then I'll give you your Senate back.
他们不能自愿回来吗
They can't come back voluntarily.
选六个演技最好的出来
Pick your six best actors.
我们不能妥协  赫克特
We can't give in, Hector.
如果你按党派路线走  我们就不会落到这个境地
We wouldn't be in this situation had you towed the party line.
门多萨先生到场
Mr. Mendoza is present.
表示抗议
Under protest.
康维尔女士到场
Ms. Cornwall is present.
表示抗议
Under protest.
厄尔曼先生到场  沃尔什先生到场
Mr. Ullman is present. Mr. Walsh is present.
道斯特女士到场
Ms. Douster is present.
哈斯先生到场
And Mr. Haas is present.
主席先生  法定人数已经够了
Mr. President, a quorum is now present.
你通过修正案吧  我会阻挠主法案的通过
You can pass the amendment. I'll just filibuster the main bill.
不  你不会的
No, you won't.
看我会不会
Watch me.
尽管我特别想看你憋两天尿的样子
As much as I'd like to see you hold your piss for two days,
但我们已经和赫克特达成协议了
we struck a deal with Hector.
替代修正案通过
The passage of the substitute amendment
主法案就也通过
constitutes passage of the main bill.
这我并不知情
I wasn't informed of that.
要多留意小字附条款  柯蒂斯
Pay attention to the fine print, Curtis.
这比协议本身重要的多
It's far more important than the selling price.
我们开始吧
Let's go.
现在立刻点名投票
I want an immediate call of the roll.
一秒钟时间都不要浪费
Don't let half a second pass.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
法定人数已经够了
A quorum is present.
关于采纳HR 934号法案的
The question is on the adoption of the substitute
替代修正案
amendment to HR 934.
赞成或是反对
The yeas and nays have been ordered,
书记官将开始点名投票
and the clerk will call the roll.
艾伯纳先生
Mr. Abner?
赞成
Aye.
艾文戴尔先生
Mr. Avendale?
赞成
Aye.
布朗先生
Mr. Brown?
我想为HR 934号法案提出一项修正案
I'd like to propose an amendment to HR 934
哈斯先生  请不要破坏秩序  点名投票已经开始
Mr. Haas, you are out of order. The roll call has begun.
书记官将会继续进行点名投票
The clerk will continue to call the roll.
布朗先生  博尔先生
Mr. Brown? Mr. Burr?
赞成
Aye.
坎特维尔女士
Ms. Cantwell?
赞成
Aye.
西里尼先生
Mr. Cerini?
赞成
Aye.
蔡斯先生
Mr. Chess?
赞成
Aye.
康维尔女士
Ms. Cornwall?
反对
Nay.
科森先生
Mr. Colson?
我很高兴你能来
I'm glad you came.
是啊  我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
你觉得怎么样
What'd you think?
音乐非常美妙
The music was really beautiful.
跟你想的不一样吗
Not what you expected?
我也不知道会是什么样
I wasn't sure what to expect.
我叫丽萨
I'm Lisa.
瑞秋  抱歉
Rachel. Sorry.
没事  我们里面有饼干和蛋糕  如果你
No. We've got cookies and cake inside, if you...
我觉得我还是...
I think I'm gonna...
如果你想见见我的一些朋友
If you want to meet some of my friends.
-行啊  好  -行吗
- Yeah. Okay. - Yeah?
-行  -走吧
- Yeah. Yeah. - Okay.
该把"奇迹创造者"写进你的简历  弗兰克
We should add "Miracle worker" to your resume, Frank.
拉撒路的魔术倒是精彩
Lazarus makes for a good magic act,
圣经故事:马大和马利亚的兄弟  死后4天耶稣使他复活
但如果那混蛋当初没死
but life would have been a lot easier
日子会轻松得多
if the bastard hadn't died in the first place.
总统本来要发脾气  但我安抚住他了
The president wanted to go ballistic, but I calmed him down.
我说  别担心  弗兰克会解决问题的
I said, "Don't worry. Frank'll pull this out.
是吗  我不会责怪你两面派  雷蒙德
Did you? I don't blame you for being two-faced, Raymond.
这是厉害的政治手腕  但不能被人发现
It's good politics, as long as you don't get caught at it.
弗兰克  如果你认为我
Now, Frank, if you think that I --
没关系  雷蒙德  主会原谅你  晚安
It's okay, Raymond. Jesus forgives you. Goodnight.
有人吗
Hello?
想来点酒吗
Care for some wine?
不用了
No.
进来点
Step in the room.
近一点  再近一点
Closer. Closer.
说一下你的名字和日期
State your name and the date.
等等  为什么  我
Wait, why? I --
请说一下你的名字和日期
State your name and the date, please.
卢卡斯·古德温  2月13日
Lucas Goodwin. February 13th.
年份
Year.
2014年
2014.
你现在或曾经在
Are you currently or have you ever been a member of the --
这是干什么
What -- what -- what is this?
你现在或曾经在
Are you currently or have you ever been a member
执法机构工作过吗
of any law enforcement agency?
我已经告诉过你我没有了
I already told you I wasn't.
两步验证
Two-step verification.
不  我没有  以前也没有
No, I'm not. And I haven't.
那你现在或曾经向执法机构
Are you currently or have you ever been
提供过情报吗
an informant for law enforcement?
没有
No.
你觉得自己被跟踪了吗
You think you might have been followed?
过去几周发生过什么奇怪的事吗
Anything strange the past few weeks?
这个...你知道吗
Th-- this is -- you know what?
这让我很不舒服
This is making me feel uncomfortable --
我们不是闹着玩的
We're not fucking around here.
如果你认为联调局没查过你的邮件
If you think the FBI hasn't been tracking your posts,
那你就太天真了
then you're naive.
你觉得他们知道我的身份吗
You think they know who I am?
不知道  你隐藏得很好
No. You hid yourself well.
你要对《先驱报》做什么
What are you going to do with the Herald.
不做什么
Nothing.
那你为什么想要访问权限
Then why did you want access?
我已经有访问权限了
I already had access.
我就是这样联系你的
It's how I contacted you in the first place.
只是想知道你是不是来真的
Just needed to know if you were serious.
那是腰果
That's Cashew.
你为什么要联系我
Why did you contact me?
因为你走投无路了
Because you're desperate.
我不喜欢当局
And I'm not fond of authority.
今天  在安德伍德副总统的主持下
Just today, under the leadership of Vice President Underwood,
参议院通过了HR 934号法案
the Senate passed HR 934,
同时通过了一个历史性的福利改革修正案
along with an historic entitlement reform amendment.
通过将正常退休和提早退休的年龄
By raising the retirement age to 68 and 65
分别提高到68和65岁
for normal and early retirement, respectively,
我们将确保未来几代人的福利得到保障
we will ensure entitlements for generations to come.
几周后  等众议院通过这项法案
And when the House passes that bill in a few weeks,
对此我完全有信心
as I fully expect it to do,
我们就能结束政府的开销冻结
we will put the government freeze to rest.
我们将继续为我们的国家服务
We will continue the business of serving our country,
而不是让国家瘫痪
rather than paralyzing it.
这是美国人民应得的
The American people deserve no less.
我们站在民主的圣坛上
We stand at the altar of democracy.
让我们站在一起
Let us stand together.
我跟杰姬谈过  我会在众议院支持你
I spoke to Jackie. You have my support in the House.
但现在众议院还没通过呢
But it hasn't passed the House yet.
在交给总统前  还长路漫漫
There's a long march before it arrives on the president's desk.
至于我  我以前总在镜头边缘
As for me, I used to be on the edge of the frame.
现在只有三英尺远了
Now I'm only three feet away.
■
一个议案先在参议院表决  然后在众议院表决
众议院表决时  可以自己起草一个版本
也可以直接拿参议院的版本进行投票
本集中弗兰克想让众议院直接拿参议院通过的版本进行表决
这样更高效  如果有两个版本
双方还得把两个版本综合在一起
各自再投票一次  然后才能给总统签字  生效成为法律
■
美国宪法规定副总统是参议院的主席
但是平时副总统不干预参议员事务
只有在投票出现平局或大的会议时才出席
而本集中弗兰克打破了常规  利用规则主持参议院投票
所以才会对多数党领袖说"就把参议院还给你"
■
2013年9月  德克萨斯州茶党参议院泰德·科鲁兹
鼓动同僚反对奥巴马医保法案
要求国会预算法案同医保法案落实挂钩
9月24日至25日  泰德·科鲁兹连续在参议院发言21小时19分钟
为茶党造出极大声势
由于科鲁兹等国会两院中的茶党成员在预算问题上坚持强硬立场
而总统奥巴马为了搞臭共和党的名声也拒绝谈判
美国联邦政府于10月1日被迫"停摆"  关张大吉
停摆持续了16天  两党在声望均遭到极大打击的情况下
不得不坐在一起  达成预算协议